Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.22
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Awards, Gifts and Memorabilia, 1950-2007; XXII.
  - Ginny Thornburgh, 14.
    - Plaque: PEOPLE-TO-PEOPLE COMMITTEE ON DISABILITYKAY ARNESON AWARD to GINNY THORNBURGH, "for pioneer efforts to increase public awareness of the architectural communication, and attitudinal barriers that limit the handicapped to worship and to encourage congregational action to remove such obstacles. She has led a Religion and Disability crusade by speaking, writing and inspiring personal example," David A. Waugh, Chairman [Blue metal inscribed plate edged in gold], June 5, 1998
    - Certificate: WE HEREBY EXPRESS OUR SINCERE APPRECIATION TO Ginny Thornburgh For Her commitment to the Independent Living Movement Awarded at the RLI Center Awards Luncheon, [In leather folder with color decoration of pine branches and cones], November 9, 1990
    - Certificate: Girl Scouts, Mrs. Ginny Thornburgh "is a Lifetime Member of the Girl Scout Movement in the United States and is entitled to all the benefits of Lifetime Membership, March 27, 1991
    - Award: Shippensburg University, Women's Political Summit "Recognizing Women Who Improve The Lives ofPennsylvanians Through Public Service" Pi Sigma Alpha Theta Gamma Chapter, March 26-27, 2002 (Oversize 181)
    - Award: Opportunity Award [Stained glass plaque with stand, Jesus with people around him], 1998
    - Award: Virginia J. Thornburgh, Sevier McCahill Award for outstanding service to youth with disabilities; presented by Disabilities International Foundation [Silver plated Oneida Revere Bowl], 1998
    - Award: The Raker Memorial Award with wooden stand;On Back: Ginny Thornburgh, Washington, D.C. [Round metal medallion on ribbon], March 22, 1990
    - Award: Helen Homans Gilbert Award for Distinguished Volunteer Service presented to Virginia Judson Thornburgh by Radcliffe College, [Press release and extended writing on certificate; Handsome lettered parchment document in leather case], May 12, 1989
    - Award: "The Americans With Disabilities Act AwardThe Task Force on the Rights and Empowerment of Americans with Disabilities Congratulates Ginny Thornburgh On her Historic Contributions to the enactment of The World's First Comprehensive Civil Rights Law for People with Disabilities", October 12, 1990
    - Plaque: Presented by Edith R. Rudolphy Residence for the Blind to Ginny Thornburgh for unselfish support in the construction of the sheltered workshop for the blind. Dedication Day [Wood backed bronze plate, boxed], October 22, 1987